ufreetv.com 2014-06-25

# About/Contact

* * *

WATCH LIVE STREAM TV, AMC LIVE STREAM, CW LIVE STREAM, CBS LIVE STREAM, NBC LIVE STREAM, ABC LIVE STREAM, FOX LIVE STREAM, CW LIVE STREAM, ABC FAMILY LIVE STREAM, FOXNEWS LIVE STREAM, BRAVO LIVE STREAM, UNIVISION LIVE STREAM, TELEMUNDO LIVE STREAM, ESPN LIVE STREAM, ESPN2 LIVE STREAM, CNN LIVE STREAM, MSNBC LIVE STREAM, SHOWTIME LIVE STREAM, HBO, TNT LIVE STREAM, SYFY LIVE STREAM, USA LIVE STREAM, FX LIVE STREAM, SPIKE LIVE STREAM, A&E LIVE STREAM, NATGEO LIVE STREAM, HISTORY LIVE STREAM, CNBC LIVE STREAM, DISCOVERY CHANNEL. and many more channels free online here.

Note: the Live streaming  channels here on ufreetv are third party content and are not broadcast by Ufreetv. The content is freely available for embedding throughout the internet and therefore any concerns should be directed at the third-party where the content originates from.

-  HOME    -     PRIVACY POLICY    -    DMCA   -  

In its early stages of development, LIVE STREAM television employed a combination of optical, mechanical and electronic technologies to capture, transmit and display a visual image. By the late 1920s, however, those employing only optical and electronic technologies were being explored. All modern television systems relied on the latter, although the knowledge gained from the work on electromechanical systems was crucial in the development of fully electronic television. In today's world live streaming can be seen on iPads, iPhones, Android devices such as Samsung Galaxy or Dell laptops or Ausus tablets and many other Mobile devices. 

_WELCOME TO_ ** _UFREETV.COM™_** _  
_ ** _  
_** **Here on UFREETV.COM you can read very informative posts regarding the Latest Tech reviews,  
Educational posts on Colleges and Universities and our Financial Posts where you can find very reliable data on   
critical financial issues facing today's world and your world.   
**_  
For the latest post on Ufreetv please visit ourHOME page  __Also you can sit back, relax and watchTv here with us.  
There are no strings attached. No signing up, Nothing to download. Nothing to install.  
Not many websites can say that!  
_  
  
To contact the UFREETV.COM team please send an email to info@ufreetv.com  
All concerns, questions, comments or suggestions are welcome. ** _UFREETV.COM   Privacy Policy_**

By using this site, you agree to the Privacy Policy of UFREETV.COM. If you do not agree to the Policy do not use this site. UFREETV.COM reviews its privacy policy periodically and reserves the right, at its discretion, to modify or remove portions of this policy at any time. This page should be reviewed periodically so that you are updated on any changes. If you want to communicate with us about our policy, please e-mail us at  info@ufreetv.com

 _  
_This Site contains links to other web sites that we do not own ("Third Party Sites"). Links to Third Party Sites are provided solely as a convenience to you and do not constitute any endorsement or sponsorship by UFREETV.COM, any information, content, products, services, advertising or other materials provided or made available on or through such sites, or the owners, operators or sponsors of such sites. You acknowledge and agree that UFREETV.COM is not responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, in connection with your use of any Third Party Sites or for any information, content, products, services, advertising or others materials provided or made available on or through such sites.

UFREETV.COM, located at http://www.ufreetv.com recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected about visitors to our sites. As a general policy, no personally identifiable information, such as your name, address or email address, is automatically collected from visitors to our sites. Personally identifiable information about visitors to our sites is collected only when knowingly and voluntarily submitted. We may collect certain non-personal information to optimize our Web pages for your computer (i.e., the identity of your Internet browser, the type of operating system you use, your IP address and the domain name of your Internet service provider). We may use such non-personal information for internal purposes, including but not limited to improving the content of our sites.  
In those instances when we do collect personally identifiable information, the following policies apply:

Notice  
UFREETV.COM will notify you if and when we are collecting personally identifiable information about you and how we intend to use it. For example, we may need to collect such information to provide you with information you requested, in connection with emails sent to us, or in connection with community postings or comments made by you.

Personal information may be disclosed in special situations where UFREETV.COM has reason to believe that doing so is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against anyone damaging, injuring, or interfering with UFREETV.COM's rights, property, users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities.UFREETV.COM may reveal information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.

Cookies  
Cookies are data that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard-drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies, which are an industry standard used by most Web sites, including those operated by UFREETV.COM, can facilitate a user's ongoing access to and use of a site. They allow us to track usage patterns and to compile data that can help us improve our content and target advertising. Our Cookies are no programs that can cause damage to a user's systems or files. If you do not want information collected through the use of Cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the Cookie feature. But you should note that Cookies may be necessary to provide you with features such as adding your personal favourites.Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on UFREETV.COM.com. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

Links to Third Party Sites  
UFREETV.COM has established many links directly to sites operated by third parties. These sites are not operated or maintained by UFREETV.COM. These sites may collect personal information from you. You should check the applicable privacy policy's of the third party site's in case you enter these sites.

UFREETV.COM contains links to third-party sites.  UFREETV.COM provides these links as a convenience and does not endorse the companies or content of any such sites. UFREETV.COM does not control and not responsible for and makes no representation and warranty and disclaims all liability with respect to any such site, any content on any such site or such site's privacy practices.

Note: the Live streaming  channels here on ufreetv are third party content and are not broadcast by Ufreetv. The content is freely available for embedding throughout the internet and therefore any concerns should be directed at the third-party where the content originates from.   
For more information or to contact UFREETV.COM please send an email addressed to 

Technical Support Team   [info@ufreetv.com](mailto:info@ufreetv.com)  
DMCA Agent:  [copyright@ufreetv.com](mailto:copyright@ufreetv.com)

Thank You for Visting **_UFREETV.COM™_**   
Peter Rip - Administrator
